<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<pfolio>
    <work>
        <image>airport_ceiling</image>
        <name>Christchurch Airport</name>
        <description>The ceiling of the new Christchurch Airport terminal.</description>
        <type>renovations</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>apartment1</image>
        <name>Bondi Apartments</name>
        <description>Challenging design conventions in beautiful Bondi.</description>
        <type>residential</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>apartment2</image>
        <name>Brooklyn Apartments</name>
        <description>Blending into the Kuringai National Park these apartments are bringing life to the region.</description>
        <type>residential</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>apartment3</image>
        <name>Little Bay Retirement Apartments</name>
        <description>This retirement village was designed with the simple goal to feel like a community.</description>
        <type>residential</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>apartment4</image>
        <name>Hurstville Apartments</name>
        <description>Simple design for modern living and to maximise the glorious vistas of Botany Bay.</description>
        <type>residential</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>apartment5</image>
        <name>Stanmore Apartments</name>
        <description>In the heart of the Inner West these apartments connect their residents with a thriving city lifestyle.</description>
        <type>residential</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>art_gallery</image>
        <name>MONA Lobby</name>
        <description>This stunning new art gallery, the pride of Tasmania, treats architecture as art to draw the visitor within its mystifying spell.</description>
        <type>renovations</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>city office block</image>
        <name>Melbourne Square</name>
        <description>This bold building sets the standard for the future development of downtown Melbourne.</description>
        <type>commercial</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>commercialrenovation</image>
        <name>Pittwater Sail Club</name>
        <description>This iconic building has been restored to save its heritage and bring it into the 21st century and again be the thriving hub of the Pittwater community.</description>
        <type>renovations</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>commercial</image>
        <name>1 Swan River</name>
        <description>With the growth of Perth comes 1 Swan River, a monument to the future global reach of the world's most isolated city.</description>
        <type>commercial</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>commercial2</image>
        <name>Macquarie Plaza</name>
        <description>This tower remembers Australia's convict past while sternly looking into the promise of Australia's future.</description>
        <type>commercial</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>dynamic office</image>
        <name>Brisbane Offices</name>
        <description>An old industrial area abandoned in the 90s was redeveloped into a bustling metropolis with the office additions for this building a key part of the renewal.</description>
        <type>commercial</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>extension</image>
        <name>Mosman Home</name>
        <description>A once humble workers cottage has been transformed into a stately family home interpreting its native heritage and environment.</description>
        <type>renovations</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>futuristic office</image>
        <name>33 Clarence St</name>
        <description>Environmental impact was the main concern of this building that has the lowest carbon footprint of any building its size in the southern hemisphere.</description>
        <type>commercial</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>glass facade</image>
        <name>1901 Broadway</name>
        <description>Our first building is still a relevant projection of the future of vibrant Surfers Paradise.</description>
        <type>commercial</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>heritage2</image>
        <name>Cactus House</name>
        <description>Inner city heritage listed facade.</description>
        <type>heritage</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>heritage</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>This old church was one of Australia's first stone buildings built outside a capital city.</description>
        <type>heritage</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>heritage_church</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>This Guatemalan landmark is one of the greatest monuments to European colonisation in Central America.</description>
        <type>heritage</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>heritage_renov</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>This beautiful old Scottish building holds the ages of Edinborough and has been brought into the 21st century to be enjoyed by future generations.</description>
        <type>heritage</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>hipped roof</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>This lovely old house has become the generous residence of a devoted family who have fused its many layers into their modern lives.</description>
        <type>renovations</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>modern triangle</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>Assigned a unique piece of land we could not imagine doing anything other than creating a unique building to complement the Melbourne skyline.</description>
        <type>commercial</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>modern_office</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>Geometry baby, it works.</description>
        <type>commercial</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>museum</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>They said make this museum beautiful to which we replied make it beautiful yourself. They said sudo make this museum beatiful to which we replied how high.</description>
        <type>heritage</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>new_development</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>This one is new, we know this because that's how we named the image.</description>
        <type>residential</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>office</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>Some people work in offices, we refuse to because we are modern and inspiring so we work in the boughs of eucalyptus trees only. We do like this office we built though, if we had to work in an office this would be the one we would work in.</description>
        <type>commercial</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>office1</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>We looked at Adelaide and we thought churches? No more churches, have an office block. It's the future people!</description>
        <type>commercial</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>open_plan</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>People love open plan, even though it makes it really hard to concentrate and be productive on your lonesome. We gave them what they wanted.</description>
        <type>commercial</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>redesign</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>What was once dark, cold, old, and positively boring has been made vibrant, aluring and downright sexy with glass and dangerous stairs.</description>
        <type>renovations</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>remodel</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>A McMansion that McDonald himself would be proud of, who needs a backyard when you can have floorspace? I know the retail value of that one.</description>
        <type>residential</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>renov2</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>We forgot to remove all bars from when this house was a prison. Wait were we meant to tell people that?</description>
        <type>renovations</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>resident1</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>London used to look a bit brown so we made it pink.</description>
        <type>residential</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>residential</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>My house (in the middle of the street).</description>
        <type>residential</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>riverside_apartment</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>Water makes everything better, even these apartments we built. We're sorry.</description>
        <type>residential</type>
    </work>
    <work>
        <image>suburban</image>
        <name></name>
        <description>This house really captures man's conflict against man, man's conflict against nature, and man's conflict against himself.</description>
        <type>residential</type>
    </work>
</pfolio>